Joao Mainardes

Miami, FL

786-521-6327 joao@crevtive.com www.crevtive.com

Summary

With 5+ years experience in digital marketing, advertising & digital media, bringing a proven knowledge of graphic and web design, creative strategy, vision, communication, sales, and management.

Offers strategic thinking for marketing and advertising initiatives and excels at motivating and inspiring teams to deliver superb creative work under tight deadlines.

Skills

Digital Marketing • Web Design • Web Development • Design Strategy • UI/UX • Branding • Graphic Design • Advertising • Creative Direction • Marketing Strategy • Strategic Planning • Management • Business Development • Innovation • Sales • Customer Service

Languages

- English: Full Professional Proficiency.
- Spanish: Native.
- Portuguese: Native.

Experience

CREVTIVE Corp. / Founder & Creative director

Miami, FL // 2014 - Present

- Lead teams and projects.
- Handled each project from beginning to end.
- Worked with each client budget and objectives in order to enhance their digital strategy.
- Produced and designed beautiful digital products for startups and leading brands.

Freelancer

Santiago, Chile // 2011 - 2014

- Web design.
- Web development.
- Graphic design.
- Branding.

_

Education

Miami Dade College / Bachelor's Degree

Miami, FL // 2016 - Present (Online)

• Business Administration - Marketing.

Google - Activate Academies

Online courses // 2015 - 2016

- Digital Marketing.
- Web Analytics.
- E-commerce.
- Cloud Computing.
- Web Development.

Miami Dade College

Miami, FL // 2014 - 2015

• EAP Program (English for Academic Purposes).